

Personal Information

Name: Boyang Yan Gender: Male DOB: July 13, 1993 **Nationality:** Chinese

Blog: yanboyang.com

Address

14-6-602 Zhuhuali Community, Huayuanxincheng Nankai District, Tianjin, China

Overview

I see myself advancing with strong ability, and passion for new technology and academic research. I have three years of working experience in Machine Learning and Software Testing at Microsoft and research institution. Also, I like to write my blog every week to share some of my new readings and findings.

Areas of Interest: Machine Learning, Computer Graphics, Simultaneous localization and mapping (SLAM)

Contact Info Tel: +86 18512290791 Wechat:

Working Experience

Mar, 2020 - Jun, 2021 Support Engineer

Microsoft, China

E-mail yanboyang713@ gmail.com

vanboyang713

The architecture of Azure public cloud to support Machine Learning algorithm, based on different Azure Service such as Azure Data Lake, Azure Batch, Azure Kubernetes, Azure Edge and Azure Networking etc.

Blog & GitHub

github.com/yanboyang713 yanboyang.com

Dec, 2018 - Mar, 2020 Algorithm Engineer

Peng Chen Laboratory, Shenzhen, China

Flight Control System Testing for fixed-wing UAV (Ardupilot), 3D Printing

Jan, 2018 - Nov, 2018 Research Assistant (Computer Science)

University of Wollongong, Australia Metamorphic Testing - Software Testing, Big Data Analysis, Natural Lan-

guage Processing





Education

Mar, 2021 - now Master of Statistics and Operations Research

Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology (RMIT), Australia

Mar, 2014 - Dec, 2017 Bachelor of Computer Science

OS Preference GNU/Linux ★★★★★ Unix ★★★★★

Windows ★★★★★

Major in Software Engineering

University of Wollongong, Australia

MacOS ★★★★★ Mar, 2013 - Mar, 2014 English for Tertiary Studies (Academic English)

University of Wollongong College, Australia

Languages Sep, 2011 - Mar, 2013 Bachelor of Business Management

Chinese ★★★★ English ★★★★ China University Of Mining And Technology

Publications

2019 **Boyang Yan**, Brian Yecies, Zhi Quan Zhou*: Metamorphic Relations for Data Validation: A Case Study of Translated Text Messages. IEEE/ACM 4th International Workshop on Metamorphic Testing (MET '19), in conjunction with the 41st International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE '19).

Patents

June 2, 2020 An automated text difference analysis and verification system/method

Principal inventor of the patent

China Patent Office Application ID: 202010489931.8

Academy Congress and Conference

May 26, 2019 Boyang Yan, Brian Yecies, Zhi Quan Zhou* - Title: Metamorphic Relations for Data Validation: A Case Study of Translated Text Messages.

(Paper Presentation and Speech)

ICSE, Montreal, Canada

August 11, 2017 Boyang Yan - Title: Human Resource Management System based on Web. (Poster)

IEEE Sections Congress (SC2017), Sydney, Australia

Awards and Achievements

2020 Microsoft Hackathon Prize

Microsoft, China

2019 First Aid CPR AED

American Heart Association

2018 The best undergraduate final project prize University of Wollongong, Australia

2018 Publicly acknowledged in the "Acknowledgements" section of following research paper:

2018 D. Pesu, Z. Q. Zhou*, J. Zhen, and D. Towey: A Monte Carlo method for metamorphic testing of machine translation services," in Proceedings of the IEEE/ACM 3rd International Workshop on Metamorphic Testing (MET '18), in conjunction with the 40th International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE '18).

2017 Amateur Radio Operator's certificate of proficiency (Standard)

The Wireless Institute of Australia (WIA)

2014, 2015 Undergraduate Excellence Scholarship

University of Wollongong, Australia